business editor Ari rabinovich joins us
now in Ari a controversial deal Inked
just last week in the health industry
has now been called off indeed so Erica
looks like that won't be happening after
all but it was only a week ago that it
was announced that manual life would be
partnering up with lah for essentially
making manual life customers for its
insurance plans uh basically some of
their drug coverage will mean they'd
have to go to a l Blas Pharmacy or to a
Shopper's Drug Mark to get those
specific prescriptions so that led to of
course lots of backlash uh for what that
could mean for competition issues but
also for customer convenience maybe if
they had a local pharmacy they preferred
it's they now have to go to one of the
big Shoppers drugmart locations or L
laws so following that backlash manual
life has reversed course and it's only
been about a week and now they say that
you can all of their insurance clients
can get whatever prescriptions they need
filled at any pharmacy yeah just so
shows how much pressure was on the them
to reverse that decision okay the bad
news just keeps coming for Boeing and I
wish I didn't have to do this so often
Erica we were talking in the break about
seems like this is getting kind of
repetitive and unfortunately it is sort
of a another issue with Boeing regarding
quality control so it happens to relate
to the exact same model plane that
happened with that Alaska Airlines
flight from last month when a door plug
blew off midair now the good news is
none of the planes that are currently
cleared for flying are affected
according to the CEO but one of the
suppliers from Boeing says that the 737
Max 9s about 50 of which that are still
in production have improperly drilled
holes for rivets according to the
statement so that's going to mean
another setback for the company after
they're just trying to recover from that
Alaska Airlines incident all right and
finally there is one part of the
Canadian economy that is growing in
Leaps and Bounds Ari indeed so just to
be uh fair right now as it stands Canada
barely if at all makes any lithium ion
on batteries but that's not what we're
talking about today what we're talking
about is where Canada sits for the
future of battery production so with
billions of dollars invested by the
federal government along with provincial
Canada is poised to be the number one
Global battery supplier according to
research firm blueberg nef it's a
commodity market and sustainable
research group so they ranked 30
countries based on where they sit for
the future of battery production Canada
came in at number one beating out China
for the first time
ever okay thanks for that report Ari
that's city news business editor arri
rovic